do this
get this on my phone
soon the day will come where I have two
monitors and I really hope that's sooner
rather than later
all right so we got 79 people already
joining the stream welcome everybody to
Nier automata this is gonna be fun okay
got it up here
okay here we go live chat is started
the music is amazing there's like five
six engines are you going to go for all
of them or endings or just the last
ending I don't know we gotta play this
game that many times but like we'll see
I mean I might play the game again in my
own time again a different ending and
then like
and then like perhaps I
will record my reactions to the ending
or whatever the Botta will see I'm
creating a new save data because my
order PlayStation died
if you guys remember when I tried
playing spider-man for the first time
but
now I got a new PlayStation so
dvg let's go
we're gonna do this a normal because you
know
players to be deniz 9s I didn't even
know you can change characters
let's go to the settings
on the game
yeah that's okay camera that's okay
screen
right that's about right I
turn down the music a tad
other okay I think we're ready to rock
that's that's done alright I start to
game dudes alright so Gees spectra King
Gaia this is my favorite game I know you
will love it thank you brawl for the
donation the super chat is real is
designed to end
we are perpetually trapped in a
never-ending spiral of life and death
is this a curse or some kind of
punishment I
often think about the God who blessed us
with this cryptic puzzle and wonder if
we'll ever have the chance to kill him
commit your hats Quadron come in to be
here all units have penetrated the
stratosphere autopilot systems green
across-the-board penetrators
sorry I had to okay done we passed the
50 kilometer threshold and are
proceeding toward the target understood
once you reach their anti air defenses
proceed to manual attack formation then
destroy the Goliath class unit by any
means necessary and gather what data you
can understood dr.
here we go this is it twelve eight
down all units activate manual mode and
rely on visuals to evade already engaged
free movement unlocked
long-range lasers confirmed Dennis come
on give me the awful are you all ready
well I nearly got wiped out by that I
played this part of the game already
about just too impatient right now got
away dude get away oh
this is cool
alert enemy unit sighted ahead Oh
sis requesting permission to engage
permission granted
yes boiling get him
whoo
Jesus down
I got this
got all you got
all right
Jesus
I swear I've played the star of this
game before I'm not even joking bro
oh yeah
okay
multiple surrounding enemy air units
confirmed requesting permission to
assume mobile configuration oh this is
where it gets epic bro check this
look at that that's so cool and I'm like
Gundams
I'm cooler on cool exam right now on the
captain
Niva like dudes if you're hype for this
series don't ya I mean how dumb do you
gotta be leave a like if you're hyped
for this series dudes I'm gonna be doing
a lot more gaming like I promise on the
challenge we're gonna do be playing this
game all the way through together
gotcha oh yeah
you know it's a square-enix game don't
you very Final Fantasy esque oh damn yo
you know when you get so sucked into a
cinematic you forget that you have to
control the game at some points yeah
that's me all over
alright alright alright leveled up dudes
level 2 not that impressive but still
you know
come on come on come on doo doo doo doo
doo
I wonder if people have tuned in to the
stream and then tuned out because we're
like this is not near like they've never
played the game before but they're
expecting to see that thick looking
character
not yet we'll get there though and she
is total babe row to be is babe
Jesus wool
can help you guys came out frickin
nowhere oh this dude
take that
slow watches a key
boom done
there's a lot of you guys here today
thank you cheering oh
this is it the epic revealed to be thank
you
excuse my pearly laughter
god damn she is total baby bro leave a
like if you think she's bay
diller/launch
detective yes I'm aware of that
that's freaking go
under suit your shoot-'em-up shoot
him up all up
that all you got come on come on
yes
I was gonna do my epic move their ball
not work using on that dude oh
we gotta be guy
and here we go here we go that's what
I'm talking about bro yes
you can't handle the power my cheeks are
oh not quite oh
yeah I remember when I played this first
time round it was so difficult I'm
probably gonna struggle again since they
only played the very start of this game
rushing get already getting close to
where I ended
but maybe not oh
I can take it to up
laser communications recovered
oh come on during program download
complete
yes finally got that move need that
whatever Jojo Oh Oh God
got it
yo yo yo yo Oh God
come on let's finish this off oh
yes you got it that was a close one oh
better make sure he's actually dead next
time that was dangerous man I
like the double acting in this I think
it's done really well your to be right
my name's 9s I'm here to provide support
copy that so was that big old buzzsaw
the Goliath you came here to take out no
just another defensive system oh well I
guess we have to find the target then
huh I've got a flight unit so take a
look around the perimeter all right I'll
work my way inside from the ground oh
she's so beautiful bro
she's so freaking brute brute brute aful
beautiful anyway let's go
welcome everyone to the freakin scream
thank you all so much for turning up you
guys are awesome
ok so we've got to shoot that
all right let's go forward
all you got that all you got dude
please don't make me laugh
I was gonna pick this up walk tuffets oh
geez
alright he's down he is down
this reminds you of God of War even what
way dude
seriously yeah what way does this remind
you of God of War I
[Music]
remember seeing one of your hair Lee
comments before his life saying that I
need to climb a ladder and just look up
her skirt I don't like Jesus Christ I
won't do that life I
might not do not life I probably will do
that life
sprin to be sprint sprint sprint to your
heart's content girl
let's go this way I think I went this
way the last time oh
and ease down
whoa I think is to do to fight up here
as far as I remember
let's go up let's go up
he's down this side
after you get this ting magic yeah there
is right on cue
whoa what the heck
Holden
yo not cool bro jeez
let's try that again
you love it
no did you get that's what I was
supposed to do god damn it oh come on
dude
that was close to me felt again whoo
let's go
exit good firm closed so open negative
nearby enemies are jamming our signal
nothing's ever easy
oh yes you got me there
I love the music there it's so cool
all right that's it
mark mark mark
don't worry do is I'm gonna get to a
certain point point in the game and then
we'll get back to the chat and interact
with some of you guys do some shout out
it's not like good stuff oh come on dude
Jesus
distracting myself
what I do guys just to say that I'm here
to interact with you all
like a freakin boss
I really should have use that move I
know I didn't know father
[Music]
you know ma'am I'm glad you're here why
scanners like me mostly work alone
scouting out enemy lines and all that -
get a partner it's kind of fun emotions
are prohibited
sorry ma'am and another thing stop
calling me ma'am ha it's unnecessary
alright then - be it is
oh geez
I totally missed
pieces of scrap metal don't worry
and he's dead he's back from up here
you see a ladder but I don't think I can
actually yeah I'm not doing it I
swear I'm not doing it
okay no no no no no no this way girl
this way oh
come on straight up that's better
fail
consider common ninja dojo
with all these spare parts
time we got a box what's in the box
goodies we got goodies whoa
can't I keep over my speed I'm too fast
for this game bro
more goodies gotcha
Oh
anybody that Tunes in on these game
streams I appreciate you very so much I
do I know like a big percentage of my
community are not really interested in
the games part of the things but it's
nice to know that there's a decent
amount of the Adar and you guys are the
MVP of the channel so don't forget that
and all these streams are always going
to be available in challenge so you can
see that you're there you can see your
chats
play sure is big I
guess humans used to use it as a weapons
Factory and now it's just crawling with
machine man - these wings - a very
purpose of the facility to increase
their overall machine production so if
we don't destroy it this strut she's got
utatsu iti destroyed this girl's got a
strut bro look at that look at oh
jeez
I supposed to go down I think no no I'm
supposed to go this way there's a door
somewhere and there we go
let's just do this Oh oh
[Music]
skip the dude did I are you angry
because I skipped you I'm sorry
there you go
let's open this box over the box now I
know earlier on today I put out a poll
between this game and Devil May Cry but
don't count Devil May Cry out yet
because as I've stated before I do plan
on playing that game all of the devil
may plays on the channel so
hopefully when a little bit more time
opens up that's gonna happen
come on let's do this getting my goodies
I like this game's approach on camera
angles as well it's very unique I mean
they don't want to change from different
views oh geez
oh come on
got'em
oh geez it's just accessing random
nonsensical data from the old world
there's no actual
machines do oh
here we go again oh here we go this is
the fun part
Oh
oh we got more you got more we got more
we go mark
more than one
I don't know what I do without my little
Joy's I
don't know what I do if you lost forever
holy crap yo we got to pause the game we
got a 60
I'm not sure what the currency is NOK
says near is awesome when are we getting
what patreon level with the full
experience be available on
when are we getting overlord like oh yes
you will when my light novel comes bro
but thank you so much for the donation
bro so shout-out to game story thank you
dude I appreciate that I haven't
received my light novel yet my volume on
light novels so
I'll just check in tell yours and just
more okay but um when I do I
hope to start as soon as I get it and I
could get it any day this week so I will
be doing a lot of the light novel
readings
but thank you for that dude totally
awesome I appreciate that
oh geez
oh gee oh my god these dudes no don't
freaking children
Goody's
all right come on
let's do this
alert bulletproof oh
close-range not that bulletproof eyes I
know
come on stop whacking me
now some of this oh yeah oh
you got you ah
hahahaha oh
okay okay
once you walk through
[Music]
whoo sweets Oh
more
are we going let's do this
let's go
and take a few of you at once there we
go
come on Oh God seriously good okay let's
just line this up correctly boom there
we go
I
look just spraying all these dudes oh
we got more
back over the right
didn't quite get that one just the way I
wanted to we have more here
there we go
and we have more year
sweet
know what I
want my goodies come on man
yes all right dude the music is just so
happy
I surveyed the entire factory but
couldn't find anything resembling our
target maybe they
moved it somewhere
maybe
well soon find out the speed of this
chick I mean wow I swear I'm not trying
to look over a skirt you know any guy
that plays this game you know for a fact
the Detroit jitan the angle just right
so they can get even just a little peak
even just a little peak
I'm not perverted at all a square Oh
goodies
you mean the birds yeah there's more
plants and animals here than there used
to be probably because the environments
changed
yeah
all right let's go yeah
well that was an accident
was I even supposed to be able to do
that
Oh
remember this part okay so I got as far
as here and I beat this part nuts as far
as I got this from what I remember
so I know this parts gonna be quite
difficult can I save it here
don't here can
no account saving is not possible yet
have you got any more goodies what's
around here no nothing but a massive
drop none there okay we shall progress
oh we got a goodie here goodie
no oh
I got more goodies down here sweet
well goodies sweet
any more hiding any more hiding
I'm sweet okay
welcome everybody to the chat welcome to
the stream we're playing near automata
look at that run a facility across that
bridge it's a bit of a hike but should
we check it out yeah sure we're here now
so we might as well roll command to get
a location wrong
this girl no she's gorgeous and that's
dangerous hmm I wouldn't bet on that I
know she's an Android or whatever what
oh
yeah I remember I struggle at this bid
and I may struggle again last time I
actually died in this bit and at the
start all over again and a really
freakin sucks and I do not want that to
happen again so
oh geez oh geez oh geez oh geez oh geez
oh geez oh geez
come on
I was totally my bad dude
oh don't like this oh I don't like this
at all oh I don't like this oh
mama oh you got me Oh got me got me
choice no no oh
little man I got hit big time that was a
total fail dude oh
no no no no oh wake up Oh
No
yes come on we got this
no no no I don't like this
Oh
oh you son of a you son of a
yes that's what I'm talking about that's
some type of a boom oh no oh no oh no
wait what
what
we're doing go dudes I need to activate
ultra instinct I know right
leerin I forgot how to dodge how do you
dodge oh
this is where near turns into
freakin transformers
Robots in Disguise
my god that's a bootleg transformer if I
ever saw one I
don't understand how he can jump so high
Oh spectra kingu yeah right we got a
super chat says hey bro I know you're
busy but have you seen Heaven's lost
property it's like the angel version of
highschool DxD no but you've got me
interested
is saving possible now don't be a dick
let me save the game
but guarantee is not no it's not isn't
it it's really not
alright first of all okay I want to go
to the controls cuz I can't remember how
to freakin dodge dude skills
weapons items requests
this doesn't even tell you how to dodge
oh yeah system oh
okay
evade are -
I've been dude
I
went straight into it
aim at the head god damn it no
no no
hey
now
now oh I like this
I don't like this at all dude
oh no oh no no no no no no no no no no
stay away balls of death
right in the face all right between the
eyes
don't hurt me why in the
kadaj no no let's celebrate you see
though oh my god
right in the face oh
no balls of death yes yes help me - me -
help me bro I need you I
do not stream on Twitch bro I'd like to
stream on Twitch now and again what the
god claim I ride on a stream here were
you guys yes I was arrived I'm
going to destroy
yes you freaking Wilson rates or
surprise
oh
my ultra instinct is lacking bro Oh big
time
Oh where's it gone
hello oh
I'm trying to evade oh
my god now it's closed
all right activate ultra instinct No
don't know old friends in Kuwait -
Turtles rinsing I cut the hair and
everything let's go I'm scared no
yes I'm okay
Hey I'm sorry Jesus No attack attack
that take it like there's no
tomorrow
no oh
stop it
that's what I'm talking about dude
I'm a piccolo so proud thank you I know
right I dodge bro $1 oh
nice
no
don't
oh right
detected no response to communications
that's not good going after him oh my
god that toshi anyway let's go
of course he's waking off
send a support request to command
negative communications have the job
sweet
oh
we got a ladder bro
you can't switch the angles would just
ladder I'm afraid sorry dudes oh
we got another letter whoo
oh he's in a bad way
- no I'm seeing you brother Oh No
No
I have to help - come on let's help them
then
pod get me starching gel and logic virus
vaccines then access possible the
subjects vital signs are too poor to
attempt a field repair
do what I think just do what she says
dude just do what she says
just go
or so Jairus
we take pride in our service
Oh
H of two to nine flight unit command 677
received usage rights transferred from
9s to to be requesting acknowledgment
please
this is pretty emotional dude this part
- bro - no
what's up what is this what's up what is
this
that is so goddamn cool dude
I want to finish this once and for all
come on
what but it is what is this ministers
ministers I
didn't know the machines have that kind
of intelligence
old friends Inc
yeah
oh
are you up for do it already
yeah I don't want to get hit by this
freakin thing again dude
she's this so strong
oh
yeah speaking role
from enemy unit marching weak point
Jesus
Janey's ice
be the control victim interpretive
infiltrating enemies nice nice
subjugation complete oh you know you're
screwed now dude
universe
do you want to get one
face oh
that's badass dude
that is but freaking us
Wow she kicks ass
whoa dude oh
this parts really sad dude
talk about bringing the battle to them
haha to be contact command request
assistance
no it doesn't look like that's your
going to be necessary oh
yeah there's many more they forgot about
this I
got to this point that's when I stopped
playing
I
don't imagine that
this is going to end well
the black box
it's ready
right
requesting
destruction of enemy hostiles be a black
box reaction
this is happening dudes
this is happening
it was an honor to fight with you
truly
the owner was mine
just like that just like that dude Oh
this game
this game dude
so silent
and now we're here
okay
that's my pod
okay no need for me to kick the pod but
you know
there's -
mission complete and all that huh the
goliaths were wiped out and we secured a
route into enemy territory
now we can
9s yeah thank you for uploading my data
to the bunker oh
yeah
Taron droids um I did that sorry I don't
remember if there wasn't a whole lot of
bandwidth down there you know I probably
only had enough time to back up your
memories mine are only intact up to the
point just before we rendezvous oh
so he doesn't remember anything
that he's been true glory to mankind
glory to my tiny juh mankind
she's touching her boob
that thye action don't you see that
theit you see you see you see that like
this game uses online functionality for
its messaging sharing features connect
to the network
yes sure
should be able to connect
yes save my current progress
dvg yes
progress is know dudes
awesome
50 1280
the year mankind's glorious history came
to a sudden and abrupt end when the
world was invaded by aliens from beyond
the stars
the aliens are leashed a new breed of
weapon machine life-forms than all but
annihilated humans I just got a
copyright claim I'm just gonna try to
Daryl survivors that's my hero academia
I swear to God
5200 480
humanity launched its counter-attack
deploying an army of androids from a
network of orbiting bases
stronger military more than a dozen
fiercely held a sense upon the enemy /
Wando haven't managed to repel the
invaders the preview got claimed that is
why you be your hub forces screen wave
media then for fake pieces of once
excuse me let's give a concise
understood sir I
wish you good hunting glory to mankind
thorry to mankind glory
[Music]
yeah yeah oh
yes here we go
they ruin my sequence I
already done the brightness the
brightness is good the brightness is
good I'm not too worried about dude
I already done this dude
okay
the brightness is said
there we go
okay
thank you
are you there can you hear me
all right are we good now yes we're good
I can hear you now ah that's really
clever though is that that's really
clever oh
thank you
anyway that takes care of the settings I
like I get options your self-destruct
permissions are missing wait a sec we
need to restore those
we don't really need to restore those I
could set it for you but you should
probably do it yourself regulations and
all you know oh
okay we'll turn on we might need it if
things go wrong during an OP you may
have to sacrifice yourself in order to
finish it so once you're finished making
adjustments you can go ahead and close
this out
okay I think I'm good
there she is oh that's her face morning
she's beautiful Oh
spectra kia kia with another $5 donation
hey sorry hey bro sorry to keep
bothering you but I was wondering will
you ever consider reacting to heaven's
lost property and I wanted to say our
channel thanks - I'll check it out bro
I'll check it out definitely but I have
a lot of stuff on the channel right now
but I'll check it out we'll see we'll
see
so we're here now the commander's put me
in charge of your maintenance ma'am that
means I'll be performing regular checks
on you from now on
that seems fair oh don't worry we 9s
models are the best around you now
though I suppose we're not exactly known
for our modesty
9s hmm what is it ma'am don't call me
ma'am ma'am yeah Hajis
there's no need to be so formal
all right if you say so oh
I almost forgot well the commander was
calling for you we'd better go see
what's up man oh to be that's better
you're learning
you're learning what's this I
can bite all we need somebody's cuz
I I use a lot I used a lot bro I
want aim did I bite him then even by 10
come on
there we go oh you have meeting
Recovery's to get look for those
melee attack up I should get some of
them as well
media defense of all your hair
definitely need some of them
HP gauge
you mean I thought we already have one
of them
why do we need boy you wanted him anyway
data
we'll need that oh I don't need two of
them one of them should be enough
minimap i have a minimap oh
I'm confused
is there a 180 I don't know dude you
know as much about this game is there an
access point to save your data you can
see access points on the close range map
be sure to save often
yeah okay
savings possible
so now I can save and that's exactly
what I'm gonna do and unfortunately
dudes I'm gonna have to cut this stream
short here because I got older stuff to
do and I want to post my Naruto reaction
for you guys in the channel
but this is basically a stream just to
open up and introduce this game so we
did it do it we have successfully played
near automata the introduction stage of
the game introduces these characters
which are really really awesome of
course we have 9s and we have to be I
know there's more characters come but
this is as far as I got on my first play
of this game that I'd done a while back
and I just never played it since so now
we have that out of the way we have that
a part of the channel now
we're going to be delving deeper into
this game I'm gonna be streaming this
game quite a lot you guys probably
wonder is that mean you're done with
spider-man not completely I know I
played the story mode I finished the
story mode that's the main thing I
wanted to do on the channel but there's
other videos I want to do like covering
the platinum trophy getting all the
suits I will be doing videos on that as
well so you guys can see them on the
channel also but that's when I get
closer to doing that in the game so when
I do I'll start recording it and
broadcasting it and then putting it on
the channel for you guys to watch so
that's gonna be exciting but this was
near automata and it was so fun I love
playing this game and I just want to say
I want to thank you all for tuning in
it's been awesome be sure to leave a
like before you go as well and of course
if you're new subscribe and hit the
notification bell if you want to get
notified when this goes live again so
you can tune in interact and then watch
the video when it goes live on the
channel so all that good stuff happening
very very soon and like I said dudes I
want to get working on my narrative
reactions I got episodes 7 & 8 coming on
the channel so get ready for that I love
them episodes they were freaking amazing
and also a quick update on the Bleach
episodes
get any time to edit those videos so
they might be delayed for later on in
the week maybe tomorrow maybe the day
after is no I have to see and overlord
you guys probably wondering the next
overload reaction yes I know tomorrow is
Tuesday but unfortunately I am stuck in
work yet again all day and I don't know
what time I'll be back out so it could
be very very late at night tomorrow
night or it could be very early hours of
the morning Wednesday morning by the
time I actually get that reaction up
there for you guys to watch so that's
just something for me to say and tell
you what anyway that does my episode of
near at elements out here today thank
you so much for tuning in i will read
the chat afterwards and interact with
you guys on the chat after but that was
this episode of near i hope you guys
enjoy like i said leave a like if you
haven't already and subscribe if you're
new and as always stay geeky stay cool
be awesome and be happy and I'll see you
dudes in my next near otamatone video
see you later dudes